University of Connecticut, Institute of Public Service Records 1998.0083
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
University of Connecticut, Institute of Public Service Records
undated, 1945-1999
1998.0083
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
2.85 Linear feet
Publications, brochures, photographs and materials associated with the programs and training offered by the University of Connecticut Institute of Public Service.
University of Connecticut. Institute of Public Service.
Scope and Content
Publications, brochures, photographs and materials associated with the programs and training offered by the University of Connecticut Institute of Public Service. One of the most well known professional development "Schools" offered by the IPS was the School for Connecticut Assessing Officers, a group that has subsequently organized and whose records are also available at the Dodd Research Center.
Arrangement
Series I: Inventory ( undated, 1945-1999 )
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to the University, its history, administration, faculty, staff and students, etc.]. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Separated Material
The following materials have been separated from the collection and cataloged:
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Acquisition Information
The materials were transferred to the University Archives periodically. The final transfer occured with the close of the Institute in 2003.
Correspondence.; Photographs.; Publications.; Storrs (Conn.)
- Series I: Inventory, undated, 1944-2000
  - School of Connecticut Municipal Finance Officers, 1945-1946 (Box 1)
  - Law making in Connecticut, 1963-1972
  - School for Connecticut Town Clerks, 1987
  - Program brochures (2), 1993-1998
  - Conference brochures, 1963-1974
  - Program materials, 1998-1999
  - School for Connecticut Assessing Officiers
    - Brochures and photographs (2), undated, 1944-1994
    - Program materials, 1944-1957
    - Facts about Property Assessment, undated, 1955-1978
    - History, undated
    - Program records, 1945-1997
    - Rosters, 1948-1994
  - Connecticut Association of Assessing Officers (Box 2)
    - Materials
      - Applications
      - Past Presidents
    - Photographs, 2000
  - IPS 50th Anniversary photographs, 1994
  - Publications and brochures, undated, 1970s-1980s
  - Certificates and awards, 1988, 1994
  - Certificates and awards, 1994 (Box OS)
  - Public Management Diploma program, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Photographs, undated, 1970s